Naoc L.B.

A Fullstack Developer and Freelancer

 Saigon, Vietnam | \times +84 947 00 2044 | \to contact@ngoclb.com

About

My name is Ngoc (Luong-Bao Ngoc) and I'm a full stack web developer with 5 years of experience in web technologies (MVC, PHP, WordPress) and over 2 years of experiences in mobile app development (lonic, NativeScript), with good knowledge of Database Design, Design Pattern, Object-Oriented Analysis and Design (see all my skills).

I really like web standards and technologies, and I have spent most of my time to work with them (Angular, Vue, ReactJS, Bootstrap, jQuery, etc...) respectively to cultivate deeper my knowledge in these standards. I always want to make all my projects more modern, beautiful, useful and steady...

At current, I am also the owner of an IT blog and working as a part-time freelancer (browse all my completed projects).

Employment

CarMD.com Corp. Mobile Developer

2014-2016 LARION Computing Web & Mobile Developer

2013-2014 TMA Solutions Junior Developer

Technical skills

PHP (incl. Yii, Laravel, Zend...) LaTeX / Markdown .NET Framework WordPress, Drupal MSSQL, MySQL, MongoDB, Git / Mercurial NodeJS UNIX Firebase...

Javascript (incl. Typescript, Ruby on Rails Docker, Vagrant

Babel, React, Angular) Java (Android) **AWS**

HTML and CSS (incl. SASS, Apache / Nginx / LiteSpeed / IIS

Shell / Bash LESS)

Projects

This App run on the Kiosks that was placed at each Shell's gas station (U.S), that can allow user run a quick **Shell Kiosk**

scan process and get their vehicle report details via email.

Angular, Ionic, Cordova, Firebase

The all-new RepairSolutions2 pairs seamlessly with our latest generation of Innova diagnostic tools, scan RepairSolutions2

tools and code readers to deliver the only complete solution from diagnosis to fix. A new in-app feature helps users identify and purchase all needed parts instantly through your favorite online retailers.

Angular, Ionic, Cordova, Firebase

AutoRater Auto Rater is a product of Innova, a prime manufacturer of diagnostic equipment for the automotive after-

market. It can assist user on purchasing a new and/or used car. The user will connect this application with the Quicklink device in the car and input current odometer. Auto rater will analysis all report data of this car and display the ranking.

AngularJS, Ionic, Cordova

RepairSolutions is a product of Innova, a prime manufacturer of diagnostic equipment for the automotive RepairSolutions after-market. This application will connect to the Quicklink device in the car, then get all information about this

car and allows user find repair solutions for vehicle-related problems.

AngularJS, Ionic, Cordova

Tenant App is a web application can help tenant of store/shop manage and support the customer instantly **Tenant Web Application**

when they send a request by their mobile device.

With this app, a tenant will know how many customer in their store, what re products that he/she interested in, all questions with the products in store...

AngularJS, Bootstrap

Storywoolf

StoryWoolf is a new publishing platform and digital marketplace where user can buy and sell great writing. All users were both readers and authors. At StoryWoolf, authors receive a majority of the sale of their work and readers can know that they are directly supporting the art they love.

Ruby on Rails, Bootstrap, MongoDB

Hulo

Hulo is an advertising application using mobile and beacon. In backend, administrator can import multiple beacons and assign to the Hulo's customer (called Hulo client). Hulo Client can login to Hulo backend and assign beacon to product so that his/her customer receive a notification and see he product's information via the mobile application while he/she is near the product/beacon.

PHP (Yii2 Framework), iOS, Android

Junior Explorers

Junior Explorers is responsive website that allow company to buy those physical mission for children. Parent can buy directly package for their children or use it as a gift for friends.

WordPress, CodeIgniter, Elasticsearch

BidCarros

BidCarros is a marketplace that can allow users can buy and/or sell new/used cars.

Drupal, Elasticsearch

Quran

Quran is a book reader application, using local data (images + music). It like a book and people can read it, bookmark a page, or share with friends via email, social network any sentences.

Java, Android

Open Source Projects

Press2Blogger Press2Blogger is a node command line application (CLI) that could help you move or backup your current

website from Wordpress to Blogger.

npm: https://www.npmjs.com/package/press2blogger

Node, oclif, Google SDK

WP PleaseWait is a wordpress plugin for PleaseWait library to display beautiful loading screen for your

WordPress site.

Github: https://github.com/lbngoc/wp-please-wait

WordPress

post2Groups (FB

MassPost)

This is an extension for Google Chrome, allow user post a message with link or media attachments to

multiple groups on Facebook.

Demo: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sn0YIWjR7yI

 ${\tt Chrome \ Extension, Facebook \ SDK}$

Mobile App Release

Page Layout

A simple project to display release versions of a mobile app, built with Vue.js and Semantic UI

Demo: https://lbngoc.github.io/simple-layout-app-release-packages

Vue, Semantic UI

Education

2014-2014 SDC, TMA Solutions (Ho Chi Minh City, VN)

2008-2013 University of Da Lat (Da Lat City, VN) Bachelor Degree of Software Engineering

Links

f Facebook

☐ Github
☐ StackOverflow
☐ Twitter
☐ In LinkedIn